alpakagear.com 2017-11-14

# Privacy Policy — ALPAKA

Your privacy is important to everyone at ALPAKA. This statement discloses the information practices for ALPAKA, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared.

This privacy policy does not apply to personal information of ALPAKA employees, partners or other staff, consultants, volunteers or other individuals assigned to ALPAKA, or to any information which is not personal information as defined in or interpreted under applicable Australian law. 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**

In general, you can visit ALPAKA on the internet without telling us who you are, and we will not need to gather any personal information about yourself. However, there may be certain times, where we or our affiliated organisations may need information from you that may identify you as an individual. Such as when creating a login account for making purchases on the website, or communicate with our staff regarding purchases or services. We may also collect credit card or bank details when you make purchases through our websites. If you are applying for a job on our website, we may also may need to collect personal information regarding your work experiences, and educational history, etc. We at ALPAKA will endeavour to notify you on how we use the information that we collect from you. If you wish to have your personal information deleted from our and our affiliates’ database, please notify us and we will take the necessary steps to fulfil your demand for privacy. Also, make sure you have the permission from the other people when you enter their information into our website. 

**DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

ALPAKA will only disclose personally identifying information to employees, contractors, and affiliated organisation provided that they;

i)                need to know these information to facilitate their services to you as a customer (i.e. disclosure of name and delivery address to courier/postal companies to allow delivery of products to you). 

ii)               have agreed that the information given to them will not be disclosed to third parties without your direct consent. 

iii)            will follow all the relevant privacy policies set out during work or contract with ALPAKA.

 **NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION**

As part of our ALPAKA’s efforts to make our services and products better for you, we will at time collect non-personal information – data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The information we collect will then be aggregated, and used to provide more useful services and products to our customers by helping us understand which parts of our website and which products are of most interest to visitors/customers. We may also provide this non personally-identifying information to our affiliates and non-affiliates. 

If we do combine personal and non-personal information, then the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.

 **FORUMS AND COMMENT BOARDS**

When you post on ALPAKA forum, chat room, or social media platforms/services, the personal information you share are visible to other users, which can be read, collected, or used by them. You are therefore responsible for the information that you share on these platforms and services. 

 **POLICY CHANGES**

ALPAKA may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in ALPAKA’s sole discretion. ALPAKA encourage visitors and customers to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you are a registered customer of ALPAKA, you will be notified of any privacy policy changes through the email that you have provided. Your continued use of ALPAKA’s products and services after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the change.
